Ukraine Ukraine is a satellite of Russia at
Украина Украина спутник России по
least it was considered in many not
крайней мере считалась во многих не не
even the emotional background has nothing to do with
даже эмоциональный фон здесь не при чём
yours here
ваш вот
but
а
in many heads it was always considered that
всегда во многих головах считалось что
this is a country that is very friendly with
это такая страна которая очень дружит с
Russia at some point it began to
Россией в какой-то момент она начала
pursue a policy of denying Russia as a
вести политику отрицания России как
state
государства
and nevi to rusm Well for example like
и неви к русм Ну например вот
this
так
Hello Oh hello you are 18 years old yes yes
Здравствуйте О здравствуйте вам 18 лет
I am from the city of Khmelnitsky where are you
есть есть Я из города Хмельницкий Вы
from I am from Voronezh Russia I understood who you
откуда я с Воронеже Россия понял кем
work for who you
работаете на кого
study I work in road
учитесь работаю в дорожном
construction
строительстве
Pony Yes there Alice tells you
Поня Да там Алиса вам подсказывает
no A
нет А
[music]
[музыка]
who is cool what brought you to chat
кто прикольно что вас привело в чат
roulette at such a late hour and not
рулетку в столь поздний час да ещё не
such a late hour
столь поздний час
here Spock probably I don’t know And you
вот Спока наверное не знаю А вас
research
исследовательская
work You have a very interesting background
работа у Вас очень интересный фон
the most interesting background Well and you are
максимально интересный фон Ну и вы тоже
not far behind either I see
не отстаёт смотрю
how there is a rented apartment What will you do I
как есть съёмная квартира Что сделаешь
understood you well continue actually
понял вы ну продолжайте собственно
researcher Today you Apparently yes And
исследователь Сегодня вы Видимо да А
you are today the object of research I am
вы сегодня объект исследования я
bored well bored about look at
скучающий хорошо скучающий об смотрите к
you as a bored object I will ask such a
вам как скучающего объекту спрошу такой
question How do you feel about that  that
вопрос Как вы относитесь к тому что
Russia attacked Ukraine is a
Россия напала на Украину
provocative question I don't know how to
провокационный вопрос не знаю как на
answer it specifically I have
него конкретно отве у меня
provocative research
провокационные исследования
Okay Okay Let's try it will
Да окей Окей Давайте попробуем это даже
probably even be more
будет наверное
interesting I'm not very literate in
интереснее Я не очень грамотный в
politics you became quietly audible I'm not
политике тебя тихо стало слышно я не
very literate in politics you can be heard well Well, and I I'm
очень грамотный в политике хорошо слышно
engaged in road construction
Занимаюсь дорожным строительством
said Yes, and I don't understand and do
сказал Да вот и мне непонятно и
n't like that such a
неприятно то что произошла такая
situation happened it's unclear and unpleasant well and
ситуация непонятно и неприятно хорошо а
what do you think who is to blame for this
как ты считаешь кто виноват в этой
incomprehensible and unpleasant
непонятной и неприятной
situation definitely not the
ситуации точно не
people I Well, let's do it let's
народ я Ну давайте вот а давайте
somehow turn it around so that you will
как-нибудь развернёт так что вы будете
ask questions to me and to mine A ok
задавать вопросы мне и к моему А хорошо
What do you think Yes you You asked such a question
Как считаете Да вы Вы же такой вопрос
Yes I think that it is the
Да я думаю что в этом
aggregate of them that is to blame I would like to
виноват совокупности их хотелось бы
say the aggregate of them I don't know Well what do
сказать совокупности их Я не
you think I
знаю Ну как вы думаете зна не не просто
know not just I don't know You are asking a question But I don't know I
не знаю Вы же задаёте вопрос А я не знаю
want not that you knew and answered And
я же хочу не что вы знали и ответили А
what did you think What are the options
что вы подумали Какие есть варианты
good that's very good Okay Well,
хорош вотт сильно
you want okay No you are asking a
А ну вы же хотите ладно Нет вы задаёте
question I will answer it
вопрос я буду на него отвечать
well I specifically If you want me to
хорошо я конкретно Если вы хотите чтобы
single out a person  there is no such person there is no
я выделил человека нет человека такого
confluence of circumstances will
нету стечение обстоятельств вам ничего
not give you anything you will say
не даст вы скажете
that this is not your question yes the course of
чтоэто не ваш вопрос да течение
circumstances the answer is not yours not to your
обстоятельств ответ не Ваш не на ваш
question it just happened that way Okay
вопрос просто так получилось Окей
Let's continue it just happened
Давайте продолжим просто так получилось
that way I don't know why I won't say you can call Medvedev okay Just look that's how the circumstances turned out It was a piece of a mountain and due to erosion it was weathered there and collapsed onto the road and crushed the bus that's what I'm ready
автобус придавило вот это чение я гото
for the question it was always considered probably that
на вопрос всегда считалось наверно что
Russia is such a satellite of Ukraine Ukraine is a
Россия это такой спутник Украина Украина
satellite of Russia at least it was considered
спутник России по крайней мере считалось
in
во
many even the emotional background during the World Cup is yours That's
многих даже эмоциональный фон при ЧМ ваш
always in many minds it was considered that
всегда во многих головах считалось что
this is such a country that is very friendly with
это такая страна которая очень дружит с
Russia at some point it began to
Россией в какой-то момент она начала
pursue a policy of denying Russia as a
вести политику отрицание России как
state
государства
and hatred of Russians Well, for example, that's how it was
и ненависть к русским Ну например вот
and
так вот и
that a conflict of interests was probably lost
что был проигран конфликт наверное
on the territory of
интересов на территории
Ukraine what I mean
Украины что я имею в виду
se This is a very difficult question I don't because I
се Это очень сложный вопрос Я не потому
formulate it poorly because I know what to
что плохо формули потому обв знаю что
answer the question I think that it's
ответь вопро Я думаю
good Russia started this conflict in the
хорошо Россия начала этот конфликт в
twenty-third
дцать третьем
[applause]
[аплодисменты]
year Well, not in the twenty-third
году Ну не в двадцать третьем
Yes  twenty-fifth twenty-fourth You
Да двадцать пятый двадцать четвёртый Вы
also wanted to rewind minus 8 years Yes, you are leading to
ещё минус 8 лет хотели отмотать Да вы к
this
этому
In the fourteenth year
ведёте в четырнадцатом году
In the year listen I have a friend
в м году послушайте У меня есть товарищ
who was there
который там был
directly on the
непосредственно на
territory of the Luhansk region
территории Луганской области
and he says that they started shooting, he
и он говорит что начали стрелять вот он
lived directly on the territory of the Luhansk
прямо жил на территории Луганской
region and says that they started shooting from the
области и говорит что начали стрелять со
Ukrainian side Why Because the Luhansk and
Украины Почему Потому что Луганская и
Donetsk regions were a very region
Донецкая область была очень регионом
that was mined there a lot of
который был добываю там же много
metal I don’t know minerals Okay
металл Я не знаю ископаемых
Here and at the same time the regions were
О'кей Вот и а при этом регионы были
subsidized and the people in this
дотационные и народу на данной
territory did not like it
территории это не понравилось
and this is your friend where is he from uh
а это у тебя друг откуда он
from the Luhansk region where
э с Луганской области откуда
exactly No I won’t say I don’t remember I myself am
именно Нет я не скажу я не помню я я сам
from the Luhansk region from the city of
с Луганской области с города
Alchevsk I will tell you Yes I don’t know what
Алчевск я тебе скажу Да не знаю что там
this one told you but after no he is a
тебе рассказал этот но после не он
fairly literate young man
достаточно грамотный молодой человек
right Gra I will tell you and after April 12,
прямо Гра Я вот скажу и после 12 апреля
fourteenth year When the
четырнадцатого года Когда произошло
Russian invasion of the Luhansk and
российское вторжение в луганскую и
Donetsk regions took place yes When the
донецкую области да Когда был захвачен
city of Slavyansk was captured We also got into it here
город Славянск У нас тоже полезли вот
these Russian military Russian Kazakhs
эти российские военные российские казахи
Yes in our city Alchevsk Yes the laws of the
Да у нас в городе Алчевск Да законы
elected mayor were removed and
избранного мэра сняли и поставили
some Russian was installed and after that they
какого-то россиянина вот после этого
said to everyone who sticks their nose out
сказали всем кто
three people were shot
расстрелян трёх человек расстреляли
publicly in the square and the rest were
публично на площади а остальных начали
thrown into basements that's all I left Alchevsk on those same days
кидать на подвалы всё я в эти же дни
for the territory that was not captured by
на территорию которая не захвачена
Russian militants that's all You
боевиками российскими вот и всё Ты мне
tell me a resident of Alchevsk some
жителю Алчевска рассказываешь какие-то
bass this is all already look everything has been known for a long time
бас это уже всё смотри уже всё давно
Yes Wagner Prigozhin already
известно Да уже Вагнер Пригожин
told gave an interview how they
рассказывал давал интервью как они за
fought for the Lugansk airport that's why
Луганский аэропорт сражались так тобто
Russia was there that's all It's been proven no
Россия была там это уже всё Доказано уже
one is hiding it here everything is clear the question
не скрывает никто тут всё понятно вопрос
what do you
как ты
think Is Russia to blame for the fact that in
считаешь Виновата ли Россия в том что на
Ukraine in what year Is Russia to blame for the fact that it
Украину в чем году Виновата ли Россия в
attacked Ukraine in what year I don't
том что напала на Украину вчем году я не
know the history except from you now
знаю истории кроме как от вас сейчас
when the word Russia attacked in what year
когда слово Россия напало в чем году на
Ukraine in such a
Украину в таком
context Well what's here look you saw
контексте Ну а что тут смотри ты ж видел
Russia at
Россия в
night grandmother
ночь бабушка
[music]
[музыка]
there is a girl girl And the girl How old is she
там девушка девушка А девушка Сколько ей
30  probably 30 girl yes And
лет 30 наверно 30 девушка да А вам
how old are you 31 And I understand you look young
сколько лет 31 А понял молодо выглядите
Listen, is it possible for a
Слушайте а можно вот так чтобы тоже
girl to also say her opinion, what does she
девушка своё мнение сказала как она
think Is Russia to blame for the attack? She has an
считает Виновата ли Россия в нападе она
acute respiratory viral infection now and that’s why she doesn’t want to get sick I understand
ОРВИ и поэтому она не хочет заболела
yes I understand ok
понял да Понял хорошо
look Russian troops invaded the
смотрите российские войска вторглись
territory of Ukraine on the night of
на территории Украины в ночь с 26 на 27
February 26-27, 2014, seizing
февраля 2014 года захватив
administrative buildings in Crimea,
административные издания в Крыму
seizing military units in Crimea and so
захватив военные части в Крыму и так
on I don’t know Well, except for what
дальше я не знаю Ну кроме как только что
you just voiced I don’t know such information
вы озвучили Я не знаю такой информации
at least in the context of Russian
по крайней мере в контексте российские
troops invading and seizing u and how did they
воска вторглись и захватили у а как они
end up there they
оказались они там
ended up there they didn’t invade no wait wait
оказались это они не вторглись нет
wait I’m a
подождите подождите подождите Я
little out of context so Well, it’s
немножечко вне контекста поэтому Ну
just that I believe you, it’s like well It’s strange, isn’t it Yeah
просто вам верить это как бы ну Странно
absolutely
правда ведь Угу абсолютно
You believe you believe Russian
Вот ты веришь ты веришь российским
sources which have been there
источникам каким
since the first days of the occupation yes Russian
с первых дней оккупации да российские
troops were there I just might not
войска там были просто могу чего-то не
know something these are different things I don’t
знать это же разные вещи я чего-то не
know something And you’re telling me now
знаю А вы сейчас мне
By the way, I’m still not with you
говорите Я кстати с вами на до сих пор
I can’t either just under  doubt what
и я не могу просто под сомнение ставить
you are saying now you can not doubt
то что вы сейчас говорите не можешь под
well do not doubt why Well
сомнение ставить хорошо не ставь почему
you said I can not doubt
Ну ты же сказал я не могу под сомнение
but I can doubt oh I
а могу под сомнение ставить
got it
ой понял это
cardina what do you
кардина как ты
think Why Russia
считаешь Зачем Россия
u yes you be new I
у да ты будь новым я
allow so what do you think Why
разрешаю значит как ты считаешь Почему
Russia is destroying Ukrainian cities
Россия уничтожает украинские города
Bakhmut Mariupol
бахмут Мариуполь
here is the city Bakhmut there were 70,000 population
вот город бахмут было 70.000 населения
wiped out to zero city
стёрли под ноль город
why did you also wipe out to zero this same
зачем вы также стёрли под ноль этот же
city Well as far as I again know how
город Ну насколько я опять же знаю как
we erased if Ukrainian troops
мы стёрли если украинские войска
were in it that is Bakhmut was
находились в нём то есть бахмут
shelled by Russians not
обстреливали россияне не
Ukrainians maybe You understand in such
украинцы может быть Понимаете в такомы
ses we discuss what you in a strong
сес обсуждаем то в чём вы в сильном
context And I about the context
контексте А я около
Yeah let's
контексте Угу давайте
approximate left from it wet
приблизительная оставила от него мокрого
spots even all the buildings were destroyed
места даже все здания разрушены
shelled question counter question
обстреляны вопрос встречный вопрос
why from the city of Sudzhi I am watching in telegram
почему из города суджи Я в телеграме
which civilians from legion
наблюдаю который мирных жителей из леги
publicly available information here which
общедоступная информация вот которая
heads
головы
as in Chechnya was once a civilian
как в Чечне было когда-то мирным жителем
and at the
и при
same time Nova
этом Нова
civilians heads can you show
мирным жителям головы можешь показать
official  the
официальные
statements of Russian officials about this
заявления российских чиновников об этом
incident are not just some kind of
происшествии не просто какие-то
production at the moment I
постановки в данный момент я даже видео
can't even
не могу
show the video That is, for
показать То есть ни на каком официальном
example, the Russian prosecutor's office did not state there
источнике например не заявляла там
even in
российс даже в
Dan it's just not even clear the heads yes I
Дан просто головы даже непонятно да я
understand why like it's not clear where it's
понимаю почему типа это непонятно где
not clear who you're getting at Yes yes yes
непонятно кто вы к этому ведёте Да да да
that is, do I understand correctly that you saw it on
то есть я правильно понимаю что ты в
some incomprehensible Telegram channel It's
каком-то непонятно каком Telegram канале
not clear what kind of video signed by it's not clear
увидел Непонятно какое видео подписанное
who filmed it's not clear when and it's
непонятно кем снятое непонятно когда и
not clear what's going on there it's not clear the
непонятно что там происходит непонятны
people who are in this video are not
люди которые на этом видео не
identified and it's not clear at all what it is and
установлены и непонятно вообще что это и
why Yes yes I understood absolutely correctly I
для чего Да да Абсолютно верно
understand correctly that it's not clear
понял я правильно понимаю что непонятно
on what basis this information
на каком основании этой информации
can be trusted at all
вообще можно
Yes but for some reason you refer to
доверять Да но почему-то вы ссылается на
it as reliable once again once again
неё как на достоверную
I'm in no way a
ещё раз ещё раз я ни в коем случае не
political scientist in no way a newsmaker
политолог ни в коем случае не ньюсмейкер
and so on and so on and so on look I
и прочее вот а ещё раз смотри я тебя
asked you a real fact when Ukraine
спросил реальный факт когда Украина
liberated the city of the court it was a court it
освободила город суду он был суджу он
was a whole all the reporters saw it and so on the
был целый это видели все репортёры и так
Armed Forces were filmed When Russia is now
дальше ВС снималось Когда Россия сейчас
captured the city of Sudzha They are filming it was
захватила город суджу Они снимают он
destroyed by Russian artillery it's a
разрушен от российской артиллерии это
fact everything is so wonderful of course the character is brutal like
факт всё вот так чудный конечно персонаж
squeak comment That's always the way
жесть лайк писка комент Вот так всегда
Yes Ukraine took the cities liberated Sudzha
Да Украина взяла города освободила суджу
liberated Kherson whole
освободила Херсон целыми
and Russia is destroying these
а Россия уничтожает эти
cities Glory to
города Слава
Ukraine write on y Telegram right now
Украине пись на й Telegram прямо зараз
axis VN
ось ВН
apok this is very and very important YouTube is busy with
апок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
us through scarg ORV in your ban and very
нас через скарг ОРВ в твый бан и дуже
many videos I don't show people at times I don't
багато вдео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about streams so that
показуе информация про стримы тому для
we can Mali tive links are written
того щоб ми Мали тивный звязок пишиться
right now and Popik there in Telegram OKM
прямо зараз а Попик там в телеграми окм
videos also interesting and useful information
видео ще теж цикава и корисна информация
and we are responsible for you trimati constant
и мы повинни з вами тримати постийний
operational links
оперативный звязок
independently in that chi will show you the process
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube Glory to Ukraine
YouTube Слава украини
write a
пиши а